<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>

    <!--Information about different tour locations in the app.-->
    <string name="temple_bar">There aren\'t very many places in Dublin where you can try a
        traditional feast of Oysters and Guinness! Or if you want a quick bite to eat, before you
        head off to do the sights of Dublin, drop in and grab a sandwich and refreshments!</string>
    <string name="buskers">Situated in the heart of Temple Bar, offers a bright and airy
        decor and a fun and lively atmosphere. Big Screens and food served all day makes Buskers a
        perfect venue for that match you can\'t miss or that after work party you have to go to.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_park">Phoenix Park lies 3 km west of the city centre, north of the
        River Liffey. Its 11 km perimeter wall encloses 707 hectares it is also one of the largest
        enclosed recreational spaces within any European capital city. It includes large areas of
        grassland and tree-lined avenues, and since the 17th century has been home to a herd of
        wild fallow deer.</string>
    <string name="SSgreen_park">St Stephen\'s Green is a city centre public park. Its current
        landscape was designed by William Sheppard, which officially opened to the public on
        Tuesday, 27 July 1880. The park is adjacent to one of Dublin\'s main shopping streets and to
        a shopping centre named for it, while on its surrounding streets are the offices of a
        number of public bodies and the city terminus of one of Dublin\'s LUAS tram lines.</string>
    <string name="tcd">Described in the Annals of Ulster in 1007 as \“the most precious object in
        the western world\”, the cultural and historical value of the Book of Kells has only
        increased in the millennium since - this exquisite work of art has stood for 1,200 years
        as the greatest example of medieval illumination. This tour starts by delving into its
        rich ornamentation and explores its dense symbolism and meaning and its merit as an
        artistic masterpiece. </string>
    <string name="tour_1916">The tour offers an insight into the events that occurred in the
        Dublin 4 locality during the 1916 Easter rebellion, an event which ultimately led to the
        formation of a twenty six county Irish Republic. On the 24th of April 1916 Padraig Pearse,
        having taken the General Post Office by force in Dublin\'s Sackville Street, (now o\'
        Connell Street) read Poblacht na hEireann (Proclamation of an Irish Republic)
        outside of the building.</string>
    <string name="kilmainham_gaol">Kilmainham Gaol is a former prison in the city. It is now a museum
        run by the Office of Public Works, an agency of the Government of Ireland. Many Irish
        revolutionaries, including the leaders of the 1916 Easter Rising, were imprisoned and
        executed in the prison by the British</string>
    <string name="little_museum_of_dublin">As a civic museum for the city of Dublin, the Little Museum chronicles the
        history of the city in the 20th century. It provides visitors with an intimate and
        informative glimpse into life in Dublin during that time period. The Little Museum,
        the “brainchild” of director Trevor White and curator Simon O\’Connor, was formed in
        April 2011 and officially opened its doors to the public in October of the same year.
        A registered charity, the museum is governed by a board that includes representatives of
        Dublin City Council and Fáilte Ireland, the national tourism development authority.</string>

    <string name="pub1">Temple Bar</string>
    <string name="pub2">Buskers</string>
    <string name="park2">St. Stephen\'s Green</string>
    <string name="tour1">1916 Rising</string>
    <string name="tour2">Book of Kells</string>
    <string name="museum1">Kilmainham Gaol</string>
    <string name="museum2">The Little Museum of Dublin</string>
    <string name="park1">Phoenix Park</string>


</resources>
